Pattern,issue,output
PS_VERB_ERROR,"Question: """""" Hi, i new here and i'm workin in some app with angular when execute the application show me this error  ""You provided an invalid object where a stream was expected"". You can provide an Observable, Promise, Array, or Iterable. any ideas ? """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" i new here and i'm workin in some app with angular when execute the application show me this error """""" uses <pattern>VB PRP this error</pattern> to show the error which the user is currently encountering. The answer is YES."
PS_NEG_ADV_ADJ,"Question: """""" Could anyone help me explain why the following code seems correct, though to me it seems like it's not? [<-CODE->] returning a string here compiles and runs though I tell it that it should be a void method SalathielGenese: that's exactly my point, the code is wrong but it doesn't give me an error to me it seems like a bug  """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" the code is wrong but it doesn't give me an error to me it seems like a bug """""" uses an undesired adjective <pattern>wrong</pattern> to indicate that there is something wrong with the code. The answer is YES."
PS_ONLY,"Question: """""" Does anyone know of a way to determine if a type could also refer to a value?  That is, if the type is of a Class, then do one conditional type branch, and if it is only an Interface or primitive then it will use the other branch. """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" and if it is only an Interface or primitive then it will use the other branch """""" uses <pattern>if it is only</pattern> to describe one condition of the example instead of describing the problem, so the answer is NO."
PS_NEG_VERB,"Question: """""" Are there performance gains to be had by breaking up a medium size component template into many smaller components w/ inputs for their relevant pieces of data? I understand the organizational benefits of having small, laser-focused components, I'm just on the fence about how granular I should be getting. """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" Are there performance gains to be had by breaking up a medium size component template into many smaller components w/ inputs for their relevant pieces of data? """""" uses an undesired verb phrase <pattern>breaking up sth</pattern> but ""breaking up a medium size component"" is the intention of the user, not the problem which the user is currently encountering, so the answer is NO."
PS_STRUGGLING,"Question: """""" I'm struggling with Nd4j.sortWithIndices(lookup_table.getSyn0().norm2(0), 0, false);. The indices are all 0. I'm trying to get the index for the glossary I think I found a way. I iterate over the glossary, useindexOf(String word) to get the indices of my words, then usegetWordVector(String word) for the vectors for my words. I then build a map from these two. """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" I'm struggling with Nd4j.sortWithIndices(lookup_table.getSyn0().norm2(0), 0, false) """""" uses <pattern>struggling with sth</pattern> to indicate that there is something wrong with ""Nd4j.sortWithIndices"". The answer is YES."
,"Question: """""" Is it possible te map users in docker-compose? I have a container that runs aswww-data and I'd like to map this user to my local user so the container can edit files in my workspace """"""
Answer: ",No sentences found to indicate the error or undesired behavior. The answer is NO.
PS_ERROR_NOUN_PHRASE,"Question: """""" Hi, I'm trying to get angular 11 working with webpack 5 so I can play around with module federation for micro-frontends. When I try to convert my main app over, I get an error when localhost tries to load the page from the main.ts file. Any ideas why it can't find this? It's in node modules ``` Uncaught Error: Cannot find module '@angular/platform-browser' at webpackMissingModule (main.js:11) ``` """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" Uncaught Error: Cannot find module '@angular/platform-browser' at webpackMissingModule """""" uses <pattern>Uncaught Error: [error message]</pattern> to indicate that there is something wrong ""when localhost tries to load the page from the main.ts file"". The answer is YES."
PS_NEG_AUX_VERB,"Question: """""" The ethereum wallet isn't finishing downloading.. Does anyone have this problem also? Stuck at Downloading block 892,148 of 4,637,826,Downloading chain structure 3,297,848 of 3,325,840 Any advice? Maybe I do need to put my laptop under the crane? XD Okay the running water was the fix. THANKS! """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" The ethereum wallet isn't finishing downloading. """""" uses <pattern>sth isn't finishing VBG</pattern> to indicate that there is something wrong with ""ethereum wallet"". The answer is YES."
PS_NEG_ADV_ADJ,"Question: """""" Anyone good with git? I'm getting some weird behavior and I can't quite make sense of it. when I do git rebase -i HEAD~3, it shows the commits in this order:  ``` commit 1 commit 2 commit 3 ```. I would expect it to be: ``` commit 3 commit 2 commit 1 ``` """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" I'm getting some weird behavior and I can't quite make sense of it. """""" uses an undesired adjective <pattern>weird</pattern> to indicate that the user is getting something wrong. The answer is YES."
PS_NEG_AUX_ADV_ADJ,"Question: """""" roychri: , can you help me out with sessions. How can I add a variable into session variable which will be available during whole session. Seems like my session variable is getting refreshed when I access any link. Here is my app.js [<-LINK->] roychri: , it's here [<-LINK->] line 23 roychri: , the data variable that added, is not available in other routes. roychri: ok. Let me have a look again Thanks """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" the data variable that added, is not available in other routes. """""" uses <pattern>not available in sth</pattern> to indicate that there is something wrong with ""data variable"". The answer is YES."
PS_NEG_ADV_ADJ,"Question: """""" I am unable to align column using jspdf. Will you please guide what should I modify in this code?  """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" I am unable to align column using jspdf. """""" uses <pattern>be unable to VB</pattern> to indicate that the user is getting something wrong. The answer is YES."
PS_NEG_VERB,"Question: """""" Hey guys, any ideas on why a test executes perfectly on a real android device, but .waitForElementById and .elementById will fail every time when I run the same exact test on SauceLabs (Android Emulator)? I'm using node bindings and the latest versions of everything. ""Error response status: 7, , NoSuchElement - An element could not be located on the page using the given search parameters"" """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" but .waitForElementById and .elementById will fail every time when I run the same exact test on SauceLabs (Android Emulator)? """""" uses <pattern>sth will fail every time</pattern> to indicate that there is something wrong with "".waitForElementById and .elementById"". The answer is YES."
PS_PROBLEM,"Question: """""" Trying to come up with a generic pattern validation directive since none is built in, but running into an issue of only getting the string name of the variable passed to the directive instead of the variable itself... any ideas? """"""
Answer:","The sentence """""" but running into an issue of only getting the string name of the variable passed to the directive instead of the variable itself """""" uses <pattern>running into an issue of VBG</pattern> to indicate that the user is getting something wrong. The answer is YES."
PS_NEG_ADV_ADJ,"Question: """""" Any idea on how to provider a service to two different lazy loaded modules in the best way? It is funny in some places (stackeroverflow) guys are saying that having services in a shared module is bad practice and others say it is the right way :D """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" It is funny in some places (stackeroverflow) guys are saying that having services in a shared module is bad practice and others say it is the right way :D """""" uses <pattern>sth is bad practice</pattern> but it is said by some other guys, not represents the user's point, so the answer is NO."
PS_NEG_AUX_VERB,"Question: """""" Hi guys, what is the next step after [<-LINK->] ? deep net for classification, prediction, sentiment analysis, yes but how to ? Only available examples do it by using already separated positive/negative data. Can't we use google Word2Vec file (1.5Go) to do that ? """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """"""  Can't we use google Word2Vec file (1.5Go) to do that ? """""" uses <pattern>can't .. VB</pattern> but this is just a rhetorical question instead of describing the problem, so the answer is NO."
PS_NEG_AUX_VERB,"Question: """""" hello, i have a problem with named router-outlet, i need to add dialogs in a named router-outlet, but as i heard from github/angular, i can't use lazy loaded modules with auxiliary routes. Is there a way to do that now? """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" i can't use lazy loaded modules with auxiliary routes. """""" uses <pattern>i can't VB</pattern> to indicate that there is something wrong with ""lazy loaded modules"". The answer is YES."
PS_NEG_AUX_VERB,"Question: """""" Hi, I think there might be a problem in MovingWindowDataSetFetcher. It calls MovingWindowMatrix.windows with flattened and addRotate both set to true. However, I think this causes a problem since a flattened matrix can't be rotated because it fails the isMatrix test. Am i mistaken? """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" I think this causes a problem since a flattened matrix can't be rotated because it fails the isMatrix test. """""" uses <pattern>sth can't be VBN</pattern> to indicate that there is something wrong with ""flattened matrix"". The answer is YES."
,"Question: """""" Hello! If I'm looking to test a component that gets a service injected via the constructor, can I just provide a mock for the service itself so that I can focus on the actual component? """"""
Answer: ",No sentences found to indicate the error or undesired behavior. The answer is NO.
PS_PROBLEM,"Question: """""" Hi! I am seeing some issues with DataVec and the stringToTimeTransform behaviour.  For example,  I tried to output the milliseconds timestamps as produced by the transform on the Basic DataVec Example data (I modified the csv to have entries where month is not only January(i.e. 01). """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" I am seeing some issues with DataVec and the stringToTimeTransform behaviour. """""" uses <pattern>seeing some issues with sth</pattern> to indicate that there is something wrong with ""DataVec and the stringToTimeTransform"". The answer is YES."
PS_VERB_ERROR,"Question: """""" Hi everyone, does anyone know how to get the mat-error and mat-hit animations? I have made a custom the mat-error and mat-hint like elements and would like to animate them exactly as in material. Thank you. """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """"""  does anyone know how to get the mat-error and mat-hit animations? """""" uses <pattern>get the mat-error</pattern> but this pattern is in the ""how-to"" question, it is only the user's expectation instead of describing the problem, so the answer is NO."
,"Question: """""" I assume the docker host has a volume to which I have to write the outcomes of a python script inside a docker container. This host volume has to be mounted on the docker container which runs the python script. But how can I get this path of this mounted host volume and put it as a ENV in the docker container? (so that the python script knows where to write its data to) """"""
Answer: ",No sentences found to indicate the error or undesired behavior. The answer is NO.
PS_NEG_AUX_VERB,"Question: """""" Hi, I just used angular 2 with the cli, it's my first try. But server live-reload doesn't work, I always have to cance the server and run it again. Is this some known problem? I tried it in vscode and webstorm. I googled around but could not finde anything. """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" But server live-reload doesn't work """""" uses <pattern>sth doesn't work</pattern> to indicate that there is something wrong with ""server live-reload"". The answer is YES."
PS_PROBLEM,"Question: """""" Im having trouble trying to update some data using and api called ""crud:crud"", I can ""get"" and ""post"" fine but ""put"" is giving me this error. How could I fix that? """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" Im having trouble trying to update some data using and api called ""crud:crud"" """""" uses <pattern>having trouble VBG</pattern> to indicate that there is something wrong when ""trying to update some data"". The answer is YES."
PS_PROBLEM,"Question: """""" Question about Observables: If I have Observable A, and things are subscribed to it, is there a way to take Observable B and merge it into A so that all of As subscriptions are notified of the elements in B? """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" Question about Observables: """""" uses <pattern>question about sth</pattern> but after the semi-colon, it is only an example to describe the user's expectation instead of describing the problem, so the answer is NO."
PS_VERB_NO,"Question: """""" any ideas on how i may be able to find the circular dependency? i tried adding the `--verbose` flag to the ng build command but that didn't really help tried using this tool [link], but it reports no circular dependencies. i've also looked through the code and nothing really stands out """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" tried using this tool [link], but it reports no circular dependencies """""" uses <pattern>reports no JJ NNS</pattern> to indicate that there is something wrong with ""this tool"". The answer is YES."
